Welcome.
欢迎。
In the last lecture, we successfully implemented this hopping up for our character.
在上一节课中，我们成功地为我们的角色实现了这种跳跃。
And before we move on, I'd like to increase the hopping distance for this animation.
在我们继续之前，我想增加这个动画的跳跃距离。
And to do that, I'm gonna first go back to my code and scroll down.
要做到这一点，我将首先返回到我的代码并向下滚动。
So for this hopup hit, I'm gonna change this value from -30 to -20.
因此，对于这个HopUp命中，我将把这个值从-30更改为-20。
I think the height of our chest is not high enough.
我觉得我们的胸围不够高。
I'm gonna click Save All, then use Live Coding.
我将单击全部保存，然后使用实时编码。
Alright Live Coding succeeded.
好的，实时编码成功。
I'm gonna try again.
我要再试一次。
So click Play.
因此，请点击播放。
Then, yeah, I think this time it looks much better.
那么，是的，我认为这一次看起来好多了。
I'm gonna try again on this side.
我要在这边再试一次。
Yeah, looking pretty cool.
是啊，看起来很酷。
And now with this hopping up ready, we just need to use the same process to add in hopping
现在跳跃准备好了，我们只需要使用相同的过程来添加跳跃
down.
放下。
And I think you are more than prepared to take it from here.
我认为你已经做好充分的准备来接手这件事。
So our last section challenge is, I'd like you to set up condition check for hopping
所以我们的最后一节挑战是，我想让你们为跳跃设置条件检查
down.
放下。
You can use the same function for checking hopping up, but only this time we'll need
您可以使用相同的函数来检查跳跃，但只有这一次我们需要
to get hold of the target position below our character.
以获得低于我们角色的目标位置。
And once you have a working condition check, same as hopping up, I'd like you to use motion
一旦你有了工作状态检查，就像跳起来一样，我希望你使用运动
morphing to set the target location for it.
变形以设置其目标位置。
Alright, pause the video now and give this a go, or come back if you need help.
好的，现在暂停视频，试一试，如果你需要帮助，可以回来。
Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
How did that go for you?
你觉得怎么样？
Hopefully, at this point you have hopping down ready.
希望在这一点上你已经准备好跳下去了。
And don't worry if you ran into any issues.
如果你遇到任何问题，也不用担心。
Let's look at how it can be done.
让我们来看看如何做到这一点。
So I'm gonna first close my project.
所以我要先结束我的项目。
Then inside of Visual Studio, I'm gonna delete these two tools.
然后在Visual Studio中，我将删除这两个工具。
I don't need to see these debug lines anymore.
我不需要再看到这些调试行了。
And next thing I'm gonna go back to my header file, and I'm gonna create two similar functions.
接下来，我将回到我的头文件，我将创建两个类似的函数。
So it's gonna be void.
所以这将是无效的。
I'm gonna call it handle, hop down.
我要把它叫做把手，跳下来。
And same as above, I'm gonna create the second function.
和上面一样，我将创建第二个函数。
It's gonna be bull.
这将会是一派胡言。
I'm gonna call it check, can, hop down.
我要把它叫做Check，Can，跳下来。
And it's gonna have the same output parameter.
它将有相同的输出参数。
And I'm gonna call this one out, hop down, target, position.
我要把这个叫出来，跳下来，目标，位置。
And I'm gonna create two function definitions.
我将创建两个函数定义。
So I'll paste the function below this check, can, hop up, and paste this one as well.
所以我会粘贴下面的函数，可以，跳起来，然后粘贴这个。
First thing in case I forget, I'm gonna call the function handle, hop down.
第一件事，如果我忘记了，我要调用函数句柄，跳下来。
So I'm gonna paste the function in here.
所以我要把这个函数粘贴到这里。
And now I don't need to see these debug functions.
现在我不需要看到这些调试函数。
I'm gonna delete all of them.
我要把它们全部删除。
So delete this one.
那就把这个删掉吧。
And this one.
还有这个。
And delete this else case.
并删除这个Else大小写。
And scroll down to this handle, hop down.
然后向下滚动到这个把手，向下跳。
So it's gonna be the same.
所以它会是一样的。
I'm gonna create an effector.
我要创建一个效应器。
I'm gonna call it hop down, target, point.
我把它叫做向下跳，目标，点。
And I'm gonna check if this can check hop down is true and pass in these variables.
我将检查这是否可以检查Hop Down是否为真，并传递这些变量。
Then same as above, we can play the montage.
然后和上面一样，我们可以玩蒙太奇了。
And instead of this function, it's actually fairly simple.
它实际上相当简单，而不是这个函数。
I'm gonna use the same function trace from my height.
我会用和我身高一样的函数轨迹。
So the length is gonna be the same, 100 units.
所以长度是一样的，100个单位。
But the offset distance.
而是偏移距离。
So after some testing, I found out that a value of -300 works the best.
因此，经过一些测试后，我发现-300的值效果最好。
You can promote this to another member variable and test it inside the Blueprint.
您可以将其提升为另一个成员变量，并在Blueprint中对其进行测试。
And I'm gonna store the return result inside of nfhit result.
并且我将把返回结果存储在nfHit结果中。
I'm gonna call it hop down, hit.
我要叫它跳下去，击球。
Then I'm gonna check.
那我去查一查。
So if this hop down hit, the B blocking hit is true, then I'm gonna assign its impact
因此，如果这一跳向下命中，B阻挡命中是真的，那么我将把它的影响
point to this outproper meter.
指着这个不合时宜的计价器。
So access the variable impact point, then return true.
因此，访问变量影响点，然后返回TRUE。
At the end of this function, I'm gonna return false.
在此函数的末尾，我将返回FALSE。
And inside of this handle, hop down.
在这个把手里面，跳下来。
So first, I'm gonna call the function setMotionWarpTarget.
因此，首先，我将调用函数setMotionWarpTarget。
And the name is gonna be this hop down target point.
名字将是这个跳跃下的目标点。
So paste it in here.
所以把它贴在这里。
The value is gonna be the variable.
值将是变量。
Then I'm gonna play the montage.
然后我要演奏蒙太奇。
And for that, I'll need another variable inside the Blueprint.
为此，我需要蓝图中的另一个变量。
So copy this one, paste it in here.
所以复制这个，粘贴到这里。
I'm gonna call this one hop down montage.
我要把这一次称为跳下蒙太奇。
Then inside of my cpp file, I'm gonna call the function playClientMontage and pass in
然后在我的cpp文件中，我将调用函数playClientMonage并传入
this hop down montage.
这一跳下蒙太奇。
And that's the coding part done.
这就是编码部分的完成。
I'm gonna try to compile first.
我要先试着汇编一下。
I have a successful compile.
我有一个成功的汇编。
I'm gonna launch my editor back.
我要把我的编辑调回来。
And next thing, I'll need to create a new montage.
接下来，我需要创建一个新的蒙太奇。
So go back to this adjusted folder.
所以回到这个调整过的文件夹。
Right mouse button, click this hop down and create an annual montage.
鼠标右键，点击此跳下并创建年度蒙太奇。
I'm gonna call this one am_hopdown.
我要把这个叫做Am_Hopdown。
And move this montage to the montages folder.
并将此蒙太奇移动到蒙太奇文件夹。
Then double click to open it.
然后双击将其打开。
So first I'm gonna change the blend option to cubic for both blending in and out.
因此，首先我要将混合选项更改为立方体，用于混合输入和输出。
Then I'm gonna right mouse button click to add in motion morphing.
然后我要用鼠标右键点击来添加运动变形。
And this motion morphing should start at here I think.
我认为，这种运动变形应该从这里开始。
And I think it should end in here.
我认为它应该在这里结束。
Alright, for this warp target name, I'm gonna change this to hop down target point and untick
好的，对于这个扭曲目标名称，我将更改为跳过目标点并取消勾选
this ignore z axis.
这会忽略z轴。
Change the easing function to cubic and untick warp rotation.
将缓动功能更改为立方体和取消勾选扭曲旋转。
Alright hit save.
好的，命中扑救。
And I'm gonna go to this character blueprint.
我要去看看这个角色蓝图。
Assign the montage in here.
在这里指定蒙太奇。
So it'll be this am_hopdown.
所以就是这个上午跳楼。
Alright click compile.
好的，点击编译。
I'm gonna test this.
我要测试一下这个。
So start glimping.
所以，开始瞥一眼吧。
Hop up.
跳起来。
Then try to hop down.
然后试着跳下来。
And you can see it's working.
你可以看到它在起作用。
And for hopping down, we don't need to do any safety check because all of our code inside
对于跳跃，我们不需要做任何安全检查，因为我们里面的所有代码
of physics climb already takes care of that.
物理攀登已经解决了这一问题。
And just like that, we have hopping up and hopping down for our glimping system.
就像这样，为了我们的闪光系统，我们有跳上跳下。
And this looks pretty cool.
这看起来很酷。
In this lecture, we handled hopping down for our glimping system.
在这堂课中，我们处理了闪光系统的跳跃。
And now with this feature added, we have a really cool glimping system.
现在添加了这一功能，我们有了一个非常酷的扫视系统。
Great job.
干得好。
I'll see you in the next lecture.
我将在下一节课上见到你。
[music]
[音乐]